<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel xmlns:os="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/"><title>jobs in ireland - Stack Overflow</title><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs</link><description>jobs in ireland - Stack Overflow</description><image><url>http://cdn.sstatic.net/Sites/stackoverflow/img/favicon.ico?v=4f32ecc8f43d</url><title>jobs in ireland - Stack Overflow</title><link>http://stackoverflow.com/jobs</link></image><os:totalResults>49</os:totalResults><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/127554/full-stack-engineer-pagefair</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/127554/full-stack-engineer-pagefair</link><a10:author><a10:name>PageFair</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>angularjs</category><category>ruby</category><category>python</category><title>Full-Stack Engineer at PageFair (Rathmines, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;PageFair is a fast growing technology company, is looking to hire Full-Stack Engineers at both junior and senior levels. These are permanent roles based in Dublin.&lt;br&gt;They are looking for someone who loves to code and is looking for a chance to accelerate their professional experience. The company is growing fast, so you will have lots of opportunities to expand your knowledge and experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate should be proficient in:&lt;br&gt;Javascript - NodeJS&lt;br&gt;Python and Ruby&lt;br&gt;MySQL and GNU/Linux-based development&lt;br&gt;Configuration management tools such as Saltstack, Chef, Puppet or Ansible&lt;br&gt;Amazon Web Services (AWS) ecosystem&lt;br&gt;It will be also good to have experience in:&lt;br&gt;NoSQL databases&lt;br&gt;Web frameworks such as Django or Ruby on rails&lt;br&gt;Functional languages such as Haskell, Erlang or Scala&lt;br&gt;Object-oriented languages such as Java or C#&lt;br&gt;Systems programming languages such as C, C++ or Rust&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;They&amp;nbsp;offer a competitive remuneration package, visa sponsorship and relocation support, employee share option scheme, flexible working hours, catered lunches, private health insurance, gym membership, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to know more about this position, please apply through the following link or get in touch directly with me via email: melissa@zartis.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 11:04:29 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-15T11:04:29Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Rathmines, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/127807/contract-front-end-developer-irish-distillers-pernod-ricard</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/127807/contract-front-end-developer-irish-distillers-pernod-ricard</link><a10:author><a10:name>Irish Distillers Pernod Ricard</a10:name></a10:author><category>html5</category><category>sass</category><category>css</category><category>javascript</category><title>Contract front-end developer at Irish Distillers Pernod Ricard (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Jameson in-house digital engineering team is expanding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Propelled by the phenomenal growth of Jameson Irish Whiskey, we're looking for a front-end developer to join our team to help us create even better digital experiences for our consumers. We're looking for a front-end developer that can&amp;nbsp;work on projects such as optimising our mobile first site, &lt;a href="https://www.jamesonwhiskey.com" rel="nofollow"&gt;jamesonwhiskey.com&lt;/a&gt;, for our&amp;nbsp;Sub-saharan African consumers to&amp;nbsp;building engaging, innovate experiences for the global&amp;nbsp;celebration of the spirit of Irishness,&amp;nbsp;St Patrick's Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an engineering&amp;nbsp;team we work very closely with our Brand Mangers in 2 week sprints to ensure we're delivering the best business value we can.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 10:52:14 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-27T10:52:14Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122608/production-engineer-facebook</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122608/production-engineer-facebook</link><a10:author><a10:name>Facebook</a10:name></a10:author><category>unix</category><category>tcp</category><category>php</category><category>python</category><category>c++</category><title>Production Engineer at Facebook (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Production Engineers at Facebook are hybrid software/systems engineers who ensure that Facebook's services run smoothly and have the capacity for future growth. They are embedded in every one of Facebook's product and infrastructure teams, and are core participants in every significant engineering effort underway in the company. Our team is comprised of varying levels of experience and backgrounds, from new grads to industry veterans. Relevant industry experience is important, but ultimately less so than your demonstrated abilities and attitude. We sail into uncharted waters every day at Facebook in Production Engineering, and we are always learning. This position is full-time and located in our Dublin, International Headquarters office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Own back-end services like our Hadoop data warehouses, front-end services like Chat and Newsfeed, infrastructure components like our Memcache infrastructure, and everything in between&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write and review code, develop documentation and capacity plans, and debug the hardest problems, live, on some of the largest and most complex systems in the world&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Together with your engineering team, you will share an on-call rotation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partnered alongside the best engineers in the industry on the coolest stuff around, the code and systems you work on will be in production and used by millions of users all around the world&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 18:26:41 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-14T18:26:41Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128093/full-stack-web-developer-help-us-transform-3d4medical-ltd</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128093/full-stack-web-developer-help-us-transform-3d4medical-ltd</link><a10:author><a10:name>3D4Medical Ltd</a10:name></a10:author><category>jquery</category><category>javascript</category><category>php</category><category>angularjs</category><category>react</category><title>Full Stack Web Developer - Help us Transform Medical Learning at 3D4Medical Ltd (Blackrock, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're looking for our next Full Stack Web Developer to join our rapidly growing development team in South Dublin. Our mission is to build the world's best 3D Medical Software. Are you up to the challenge?&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 12:21:15 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-03T12:21:15Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Blackrock, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120826/software-delivery-manager-bearingpoint-ireland</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120826/software-delivery-manager-bearingpoint-ireland</link><a10:author><a10:name>BearingPoint Ireland</a10:name></a10:author><category>agile</category><category>scrum</category><category>kanban</category><title>Software Delivery Manager at BearingPoint Ireland (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At BearingPoint Ireland, we are growing quickly and have a number of exciting new projects to challenge the very best Developers. We are working with a wide range of clients, on a number of complex projects that are transforming the way business is being done in Ireland. We are looking for talented Development Leads to join our Software Development team. As a Development Lead, you will join a team delivering a range of enterprise and web/mobile solutions for our clients using the latest technologies and Agile methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We currently have an opportunity in our Dublin office for a Development Lead. In this role, you will work closely with Development, QA, Analysis, Project Management and Architecture personnel in on large scale delivery projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role will involve:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading software delivery projects from an organisational and planning perspective&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adapting and implementing Agile oriented delivery methodologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Liaising with clients and senior project stakeholders on project matters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Team coaching and mentoring&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:41:01 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-18T11:41:01Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/115526/senior-front-end-developer-3d-issue-ltd</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/115526/senior-front-end-developer-3d-issue-ltd</link><a10:author><a10:name>3D Issue LTD</a10:name></a10:author><category>html5</category><category>javascript</category><category>mysql</category><category>css3</category><category>jquery</category><title>Senior Front End Developer at 3D Issue LTD (Letterkenny, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are an organically grown team&amp;nbsp;with over 25 staff developing disruptive tools for the digital publishing / content marketing sectors. We're 10 years old but we still retain our start-up ethos. &amp;nbsp;We believe in working in small teams developing great products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;3D Issue has built a following of over 15,000 customers including the likes of eBay, Google, NASA and Mensa to name a few. &amp;nbsp;We have a dynamic, innovative, hard-working and fun&amp;nbsp;team who are responsible for designing, developing and launching enterprise mobile apps for&amp;nbsp;the digital publishing&amp;nbsp;/&amp;nbsp;content marketing markets.&amp;nbsp;You&amp;nbsp;will have the ability to work in a fast paced and dynamic work environment and must be willing to take direction and implement changes as and when required to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your responsibilities will include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Participate in the architecture, design, development and launching of enterprise web applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure that all technical requirements are identified, estimated, designed and implemented.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the analysts, designers, testing and support teams to ensure all technical&amp;nbsp;requirements for new projects are captured, designed and developed accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write and perform unit and integration tests.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with team members and other teams and integrate individual components into&amp;nbsp;complex enterprise&amp;nbsp;systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work independently on assigned components and tasks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain existing web applications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify and resolve any production issues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work in a fast paced environment and deliver production quality software within tight schedules.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure any customer issues are resolved quickly by applying solutions to any identified problems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 11:38:08 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-27T11:38:08Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Letterkenny, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120789/web-developer-front-end-pokerstars</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120789/web-developer-front-end-pokerstars</link><a10:author><a10:name>Pokerstars</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>html</category><category>angularjs</category><category>css</category><title>Web Developer Front-End at Pokerstars (Loughlinstown, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Are you a Web Developer looking to work at the forefront of technology and innovative products used by millions of players?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you will be developing and maintaining systems to enable people to have fun, we strongly believe you in turn should have fun doing this. So we have an onsite pool and foosball table and a gym (that&amp;rsquo;s fun for some people!)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Focusing more on the job itself, as one of our highly skilled Web Developers, you will analyse user requirements and produce corresponding development tasks, ensuring their completion by putting together a robust end to end process. You will maintain our existing systems, develop new system applications and improve functionality to ensure high quality in any software releases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will also be working on innovative projects such as: Real Time CRM, Marketing Platforms, Customer Messaging Systems, Web based Store, Back office applications and dashboards for our business customers etc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Web Developer job is based in our Dublin service office forming part of our Software Development Services team. As part of this team, you will provide contract research and development services to our gaming companies. And trust us, there are plenty of pioneering projects across the Group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The salary for this job is based on experience, so whilst we are not able to go into detail at this stage, we can say that we offer great salary packages and also like to throw in a discretionary annual performance bonus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We offer health and dental insurance for you, your partner and your children (if you all live at the same address). In addition, you are entitled to an annual health assessment and to join our company pension scheme.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our in-house training and development team deliver fantastic support in terms of developing your skills and helping you progress your career.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have a canteen which offers hot and cold options for breakfast and lunch and we contribute &amp;euro;3 daily towards this. In addition, there is free fresh fruit, snacks and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 08:34:21 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-11T08:34:21Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Loughlinstown, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122315/senior-js-reactjs-front-end-software-engineer-rapid7</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122315/senior-js-reactjs-front-end-software-engineer-rapid7</link><a10:author><a10:name>Rapid7</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>reactjs</category><category>angularjs</category><category>python</category><category>postgresql</category><title>Senior JS / ReactJS Front-End Software Engineer: Log Management &amp; Analysis at Rapid7 (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented and experienced Senior Software Engineer with a strong background in the design and implementation of modern front-end systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be a front-end focused full stack web developer with experience in modern JavaScript frameworks, in particular ReactJS. You must have a passion for solving extremely challenging problems and shipping high quality code. You will work within our engineering teams to design, build and deliver new product features and continually drive improvements in system design, scalability and performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As much as the previous experience is key, a strong mind and work ethic are the most important factors. At Logentries by Rapid7, we value intellectual curiosity, a passion for technology, initiative, and a good sense of humour.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 16:51:14 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-02T16:51:14Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/127122/ms-dynamics-developer-bearingpoint-ireland</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/127122/ms-dynamics-developer-bearingpoint-ireland</link><a10:author><a10:name>BearingPoint Ireland</a10:name></a10:author><category>dynamics-crm-2015</category><category>adxstudio-portals</category><category>sql</category><category>.net</category><category>reporting-services</category><title>MS Dynamics Developer at BearingPoint Ireland (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are currently recruiting CRM Technical Consultants for our growing Microsoft Dynamics practice. The CRM Developer will be a senior technical resource responsible for planning, designing, and leading the implementation of CRM solutions and ADX Portals for our clients. Coming from a strong Microsoft development background, you will be expected to have broad and deep technical skills and experience designing and implementing enterprise solutions based on the Dynamics platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 12:25:58 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-18T12:25:58Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/107593/java-developer-all-levels-bearingpoint-ireland</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/107593/java-developer-all-levels-bearingpoint-ireland</link><a10:author><a10:name>BearingPoint Ireland</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><category>spring</category><category>hibernate</category><category>jsf</category><category>ejb-3.0</category><title>Java Developer - All Levels at BearingPoint Ireland (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;BearingPoint Ireland has exciting new projects to challenge the very best Java Developers. &amp;nbsp;We are working with a wide range of clients, on a number of projects that are transforming the way business is being done in Ireland and across Europe. &amp;nbsp;We are expanding our team and are current looking for talented Java Developers to join us.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:27:30 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-18T11:27:30Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/119883/use-intercom-for-personal-fun-challenging-intercom</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/119883/use-intercom-for-personal-fun-challenging-intercom</link><a10:author><a10:name>Intercom</a10:name></a10:author><category>javascript</category><category>ruby</category><category>ember.js</category><category>java</category><category>python</category><title>Use Intercom for personal, fun &amp; challenging engineering support! at Intercom (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT'S THE OPPORTUNITY?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you have a strong need to understand how and why things work the way they do? Are you acutely aware of customer experience and upset when a company you&amp;rsquo;re dealing with lets you down?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have some engineering or web development experience and want to be a part of creating truly exceptional customer experiences then the Customer Support team at Intercom is right for you. We're looking for a support engineer to work an offset week, &lt;strong&gt;working three days in the office, remotely both weekend days and taking off two days during the week&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intercom supports over 13k businesses ranging from bootstrapped startups to large enterprise corporations. Our Support Engineers partner with our customers to tackle the challenging technical issues they face in innovative ways. In this role, you will be directly responsible for helping people integrate Intercom into their products, diagnose and report problems they have, and serve as the bridge between our customers and our product teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://blog.intercom.io/intercom-customer-support/" rel="nofollow"&gt;We use Intercom to support Intercom customers&lt;/a&gt;, so whether you&amp;rsquo;re just starting out in your career or want to get a deeper understanding of fundamental customer motivations and how those are applied to building an ambitious, world-class product, this role provides that great opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have all experienced terrible customer service. Robotic agents running through a script of predetermined messages, never helping or sympathizing, just programmatically following instructions. That&amp;rsquo;s the opposite of who we are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our way of providing support is based on the &lt;a href="https://blog.intercom.io/rebuilding-support-around-continuity-trust/" rel="nofollow"&gt;principles of continuity and trust&lt;/a&gt; and our style of communication is personal, friendly and fun. We engage in dynamic conversations with our customers and are big fans of visual communication (think emojis, stickers, GIFs) - we believe that &lt;a href="https://blog.intercom.io/visual-media-customer-support/" rel="nofollow"&gt;visual support is human support&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WILL I BE DOING?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this role you will:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Debug complex issues with an understanding of both our own codebase and the many technologies employed by our customers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solve technical problems for customers on a daily basis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Utilize inherited and learned technical knowledge (including but not limited to: Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Ember.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Redis, Pusher, nginx, Sinatra, Sidekiq, and lots more) to build tools that will help increase the efficiency and effectiveness of the team and its processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Influence the direction of the Intercom product through daily communication with our customers and consistent collaboration with our product teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 09:30:15 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-27T09:30:15Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125433/sr-backend-developer-php-with-ad-tech-experience-stark-ventures-ltd</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125433/sr-backend-developer-php-with-ad-tech-experience-stark-ventures-ltd</link><a10:author><a10:name>Stark Ventures LTD</a10:name></a10:author><category>php</category><category>symfony2</category><category>mongodb</category><category>javascript</category><category>bigquery</category><title>Sr Backend Developer (PHP) with Ad Tech experience at Stark Ventures LTD (Dublin, Irland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Stark Ventures is an incubator for start-ups in the Ad Tech industry. The two start ups within our family include Koneo Mobile Inc and Mobmonkey Ltd. We are focusing on mobile marketing and our technology includes&amp;nbsp;high load, low latency systems that are highly available and scalable - think ad servers (mobile/online, video, reengagement), real time bidder for programmatic buying, client and campaign management as well as tracking solutions. Our technology and expertise spans across the entire Ad Tech ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you join us, you will take on responsibility from day one. Working in a small team with an agile workflow, you will have a direct impact in shaping our products, contributing to multiple components and taking full ownership of the various development projects.&amp;nbsp;We are flexible in terms of working hours, however we are looking for someone to be based in either one of our European locations;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Dublin or Berlin&lt;/strong&gt;. Working from home is an option but you must be available and able to work onsite at least 2-3 days a week as needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we continue to scale our technology, we continuously face big technological challenges that we must overcome by pushing the known boundaries, never stop questioning, be afraid of testing different technologies and working together as a team to find these solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced and passionate&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Backend Developer (PHP)&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for continuously&amp;nbsp;improving&amp;nbsp;our service oriented backend system and optimizing the code and database for high performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Develop, improve, and maintain our backend system&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Design and implement scalable, clean solutions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Process and analyze large datasets&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Identify the utilization of new technologies, active involvement in providing solutions to technical challenges&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 19:53:56 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-22T19:53:56Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Irland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126312/automation-dev-cloud-exp-needed-asap-near-intergraph-uk-ltd-hostsure</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126312/automation-dev-cloud-exp-needed-asap-near-intergraph-uk-ltd-hostsure</link><a10:author><a10:name>Intergraph UK Ltd - Hostsure</a10:name></a10:author><category>powershell</category><category>.net</category><category>azure</category><category>cloud</category><category>dsc</category><title>Automation Dev (Cloud exp) needed asap - near Swindon, Dublin or Derry at Intergraph UK Ltd - Hostsure (Dublin, Ireland) (allows remote)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Automation Developer is an integral member of the SmartPlant Cloud Automation team and key to ensuring on time and quality project delivery. Supporting the other team members and management, the individual will work on a variety of projects including setup, configuration and testing of automation framework components, PowerShell module scripting, Workflow analysis and design, Workflow Scripting as well as assisting in Research and Development efforts during Proof of Concept phases designed to enhance the Automation framework. Additionally, the Developer will help coach non-developer team members to improve their PowerShell Coding and module creation where possible with a focus on code quality and adherence to team standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is expected that the role will be developed to the individual&amp;rsquo;s strength&amp;rsquo;s and become more specialised over time, particularly where a natural aptitude or desire is shown towards a specific area or application.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop required PowerShell Modules and Azure Automation Runbooks in accordance with best practices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Produce documentation supporting the development lifecycle.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the automation framework and methodology development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support and learn from automation engineers and developers in a variety of automation workflows.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coach non-developer team members in development methodologies and best practices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attend regular project, team and customer meetings where required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Liaise with Microsoft Azure Teams when required to help deploy new features and enhancements released on the Azure Automation platform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in R&amp;amp;D efforts to improve methods, toolsets and processes used by the automation team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support Automation Workflows and code throughout its lifecycle from Development to Test/Integration and then into the Production environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intergraph Process, Power &amp;amp; Marine (PP&amp;amp;M) offers challenging work and a global team environment where your opinion counts. We also offer a competitive compensation and benefits package including opportunities for professional development and learning. To learn more about our company visit www.intergraph.com. To view all of our EMIA region employment opportunities or to apply for this job visit http://www.intergraph.com/careers/emia/default.aspx&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 14:26:17 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-05T14:26:17Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120834/net-software-developer-bearingpoint-ireland</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120834/net-software-developer-bearingpoint-ireland</link><a10:author><a10:name>BearingPoint Ireland</a10:name></a10:author><category>vb.net</category><category>asp.net-mvc</category><category>wcf</category><category>entity-framework</category><category>sql</category><title>.NET Software Developer at BearingPoint Ireland (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At BearingPoint Ireland, we are growing quickly and have a number of exciting new projects to challenge the very best Developers. We are working with a wide range of clients, on a number of complex projects that are transforming the way business is being done in Ireland. We are looking for talented .NET Developers to join our Software Development team. As a .NET Developer, you will join a team delivering a range of enterprise and web solutions for our clients using the latest technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsibility for design and implementation of software projects and play a key role in ensuring the quality of solutions we build.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:33:28 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-18T11:33:28Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114055/graduate-software-engineers-required-for-fast-arista-networks-inc</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114055/graduate-software-engineers-required-for-fast-arista-networks-inc</link><a10:author><a10:name>Arista Networks Inc.</a10:name></a10:author><category>performance</category><category>java</category><category>parallel-processing</category><category>matlab</category><category>c++</category><title>Graduate Software Engineers required for fast growing office in Dublin at Arista Networks Inc. (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a Graduate Software Engineer your core responsibility is to deliver new product features. A major part of this is writing and owning the code that drives our products. But the role of a C++ Software Engineer is much bigger than &amp;lsquo;simply&amp;rsquo; writing code. Software Engineers work on the whole development process, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;suggesting and deciding what features to build&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;driving the design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;writing the code (of course)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;pushing, testing, documenting the feature&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engineering Driven. Our engineers have full ownership of their projects. Our management structure is flat and lightweight. Software engineering is run by software engineers -- you are in charge of delivering your work from design to code to test to customer shipment. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insane amount of automation! We put a premium on building and using tools that make everyone super-productive. This translates into quicker turnaround times on new features and products for increased revenue with smaller teams. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We value openness. No part of the company is off-limits, meaning that our engineers have the chance to work on a variety of different areas. Our interns have the same responsibility as our full timers who have the same responsibility as our old timers and all get to work side-by-side on important, customer-impacting projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 06:36:49 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-24T06:36:49Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125622/qa-automation-engineer-at-irelands-leading-distilled-sch</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125622/qa-automation-engineer-at-irelands-leading-distilled-sch</link><a10:author><a10:name>Distilled SCH</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>javascript</category><title>QA Automation Engineer at Ireland's Leading Property Website - Daft! at Distilled SCH (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Daft is Ireland&amp;rsquo;s leading property portal. Founded in 1997, it has revolutionised how consumers in Ireland find property. Nine out of ten properties for sale in Ireland are advertised on Daft, and it attracts over 2 million unique visitors and 250 million page impressions per month across multiple channels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a QA Automation Engineer to help us build and integrate our testing environment on Web Applications. You&amp;rsquo;ll be working with the development, commercial and design teams in supporting the product strategy. In Daft members of the technology team are encouraged to voice their creative ideas and watch them become initiatives and part of the solution. You will tackle challenging, novel solutions every day and you will be an integral member of the technology team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities will include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reporting to the QA Engineer, you will ensure that our applications are up to standard before releasing to the public.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with a variety of automated test tools &amp;ndash; these may include Selenium WebDriver, BDD, Jenkins, Java, Python, PostMan / SoapUI etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working closely with the Web team in the definition of the Acceptance tests.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accepting and managing any manual QA-related activity including test case creation, execution when required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Following established coding standards and techniques and assist with establishing standards.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Researching latest tools, techniques, resources and methodologies and constantly contributing to best practice processes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Suggesting and implementing improvements to frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documenting framework changes and best practices for our organisation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benefits&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A fast-paced, challenging and fun working environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;An attractive salary and benefits package and career development plan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to work with one of Ireland's most known Internet companies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Quarterly hack days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Friday treats&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Discounted parking available&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The chance to make a lasting difference. The projects are exciting and you will be given wide scope for creativity and innovation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 13:36:09 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-26T13:36:09Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/98374/senior-net-developer-at-dublins-hottest-travel-roomex</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/98374/senior-net-developer-at-dublins-hottest-travel-roomex</link><a10:author><a10:name>Roomex</a10:name></a10:author><category>c#</category><category>rest</category><category>git</category><category>microservices</category><category>domain-driven-design</category><title>Senior .NET Developer at Dublin's Hottest Travel Company at Roomex (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're looking for a Senior Developer with experience to join our Development team in Dublin. You should have 'strong drive' and be able and willing to work in an agile, modern and fast moving environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the position&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A successful candidate will be a team player who can take responsibility for building, delivering, testing and deploying new core projects through to production. You will take ownership of new products and features such as:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Helping to build out our microservices architecture.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing new strategies to improve search system responsivieness and&amp;nbsp;performance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refining our backoffice systems which service and manage hotel reservations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;nbsp;don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;nbsp;hire based on experience with a handful of tools. Instead, we want smart, capable, and experienced people who can learn our tools quickly (and suggest new ones!). Prior experience with our stack or similar is however is a bonus. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we use:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft technology on server side frontend and middle tiers (.NET, C#, ASP.NET MVC, SQL Server).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;JSON based public and internal&amp;nbsp;services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;PubSub and Queue based processes for cache reloading and long running tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Git source control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;SeleniumJS testing framework.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continuous Integration with integrated testing allowing us to deploy to live, with confidence, multiple times a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although most of our core logic is written in C#, in Roomex we use the right tool for the job when it makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have lots of exciting challenges which need to be solved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We value our people...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Salaries are generous with good holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roomex is growing fast and launching into new markets. We're looking for people who are interested in rolling up their sleeves and getting stuck in to building some amazing software which we believe will transform the corporate travel industry. If this sounds like the kind of challenge you are interested in then please get in touch.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 09:35:21 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-05T09:35:21Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120821/devops-engineer-java-bearingpoint-ireland</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120821/devops-engineer-java-bearingpoint-ireland</link><a10:author><a10:name>BearingPoint Ireland</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><category>unix</category><category>jenkins</category><category>maven</category><category>junit</category><category>sysadmin</category><title>DevOps Engineer (Java) at BearingPoint Ireland (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At BearingPoint Ireland, we are growing quickly and have a number of exciting new projects to challenge the very best DevOps Engineers. We are working with a wide range of clients, on a number of complex projects that are transforming the way business is being done in Ireland.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The DevOps Engineer (Java) will be responsible for maintaining and improving an enterprise continuous integration / delivery framework. This person is responsible for recommending, developing, and implementing the automated frameworks to maximize the efficiency of the build and release process. You will work within an Agile delivery environment and support multiple project teams and codebases to enable the deployment of application releases to controlled test and production environments.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We currently have an exciting opportunity in our Dublin office for a DevOps Engineer. As a DevOps Engineer, you will work within our Release Management Team and work closely with the Development and QA Teams on all software builds and releases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role will involve:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaboration with Software Development, QA Engineers, and System Architects to continuously improve the efficiency and reliability of build and deployment processes to support all phases of development, QA and production releases.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing and maintaining a detailed understanding of the structure and inter-dependencies of systems and leverage this knowledge to improve our build and release processes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintaining and enhancing our Continuous Integration environment on a real-time basis, monitoring builds, maintaining configuration, and developing automation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrating expertise in a range of automation tools and approaches in a Unix environment (e.g. Jenkins/TeamCity, Maven, Ansible), as well as other scripting languages.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Automating the build, Continuous Integration (CI) and deployment processes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supporting automated build, release &amp;amp; test solutions, internal tools development for automation, maintenance of build environments, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinating releases including pre-release checks, validation of release change sets,&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; release schedule, code freeze, SVN to GIT migration, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creation of new environments and updates to these environments including configuration of Jenkins and application support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid experience of the SVN/GIT, Jenkins/TeamCity for Continuous Integration builds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with DevOps methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with rapidly troubleshooting application configuration issues in Unix environments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:32:45 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-18T11:32:45Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125620/software-developer-at-one-of-irelands-leading-distilled-sch</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125620/software-developer-at-one-of-irelands-leading-distilled-sch</link><a10:author><a10:name>Distilled SCH</a10:name></a10:author><category>mysql</category><category>php</category><category>mongodb</category><category>solr</category><category>elasticsearch</category><title>Software Developer at one of Ireland's leading classified websites - Adverts.ie! at Distilled SCH (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're Ireland's strongest company in Online Classified Advertising. &amp;nbsp;One of our brands, Adverts.ie is looking for a new Software Developer to join the Development Team! &amp;nbsp;This is where you come in...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a member of the Adverts.ie development team, you will be working on site features that are used by thousands of people across multiple devices and platforms. You'll get to make the most of your experience by having input to every stage of the product development lifecycle. We have a very high standard on our development team and are looking for smart, passionate developers. The role is an extremely rewarding one for the right candidate, as you will be given ownership over your own projects from day one.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 13:27:34 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-26T13:27:34Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125164/engineering-manager-mentor-ambitious-engineers-intercom</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/125164/engineering-manager-mentor-ambitious-engineers-intercom</link><a10:author><a10:name>Intercom</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>ruby</category><category>ember.js</category><category>mysql</category><category>java</category><title>Engineering Manager - Mentor ambitious engineers, develop strategy &amp; write code at Intercom (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Intercom is growing fast. We&amp;rsquo;ve created an environment where product teams, with big ambitions, can ship high quality product to our customers every week. Across a team of more than 60 engineers, we ship changes to production around 100 times each weekday. Our mission is to make web and mobile business personal. Come help us build a world changing product, a long lasting company and the most effective R&amp;amp;D team possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re particularly focused on building an organisation where people thrive, grow in their careers, and enjoy having high impact through their work. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for experienced engineering managers to help us grow our capabilities and capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Intercom platform comprises of several different and connected products. Each product is designed and developed &amp;mdash; through invention and iteration &amp;mdash; by a single team. As an engineering manager you&amp;rsquo;ll partner with a product manager to define a product vision, strategy and roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be expected to own your space: work with all disciplines on your team to build, launch and iterate. Talk directly with your customers, take part in usability studies, work with data analysts and researchers to ask the right questions and make good use of the answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an incredibly rare opportunity to join a company that&amp;rsquo;s still small but on its way to something much bigger, with a meaningful transformative mission. You&amp;rsquo;ll work directly with a product, design, and engineering team who&amp;rsquo;ve worked in places such as Amazon, Facebook, Google, Apple and Zendesk. And best of all, be early enough to hold a leadership position where you have a high impact role in our success over the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This role is based in our city centre office on St. Stephen&amp;rsquo;s Green, in Dublin, Ireland. Our entire R&amp;amp;D team is based here. You'll report directly to one of our directors of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will I be doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaboratively set a &lt;a href="https://blog.intercom.io/666-product-roadmap/" rel="nofollow"&gt;product and technical direction&lt;/a&gt; with your team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support an ambitious group of engineers in their career goals. Work with our people ops team to maintain our high performance and high morale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be actively involved in hiring and growing our engineering team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Care about agility as much you care for scalability and availability. Continuous deployment keeps us focused on incremental releases. Even our biggest technical achievements roll out piece by piece, feature flagged out of sight. Projects are kept short and tightly scoped. Teams&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://blog.intercom.io/shipping-is-your-companys-heartbeat/" rel="nofollow"&gt;build a weekly cadence&lt;/a&gt; of releases.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drive, create and improve operational excellence, quality, security and privacy initiatives within your team and the entire engineering organization.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help us evolve our culture.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 14:44:51 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-19T14:44:51Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109385/senior-mobile-developer-android-or-ios-hubspot</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109385/senior-mobile-developer-android-or-ios-hubspot</link><a10:author><a10:name>HubSpot</a10:name></a10:author><category>android</category><category>kotlin</category><category>rx-java</category><category>ios</category><category>swift</category><title>Senior Mobile Developer -&gt; Android or iOS at HubSpot (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;HubSpot users rely on mobile because it's key to the way modern businesses run. Now that we do most of our work online, marketers and salespeople can do their jobs from anywhere. That means they need the power of HubSpot to engage with contacts, prospects, and customers when they're not at their desks. Cue the &lt;a href="http://www.hubspot.com/products/mobile" rel="nofollow"&gt;HubSpot mobile team&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're a small team with big goals. We want to empower our users to grow their businesses from their phones, create an intuitive mobile experience, and help teams collaborate through the HubSpot mobile app. So far, we've made an impact by identifying which use cases are most valuable for users on-the-go (for example, the social media tool for publishing and monitoring real-time social content) and building features that compliment the desktop experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We work closely with our product manager and designers to set the vision for what we build. Next, we're building new additions to the mobile experience that will make collaboration and communication between teams, prospects, and customers easier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're proud of our mobile tech stack and are keen to contribute to the community through &lt;a href="http://github.hubspot.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;open source projects&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://product.hubspot.com/blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;HubSpot Product Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 15:57:31 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-26T15:57:31Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128464/front-end-development-lead-accenture-centre-for</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128464/front-end-development-lead-accenture-centre-for</link><a10:author><a10:name>Accenture Centre for Innovation</a10:name></a10:author><category>html5</category><category>css3</category><category>javascript</category><category>node.js</category><category>angularjs</category><title>Front End Development Lead at Accenture Centre for Innovation (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At our Centre for Innovation in Dublin, we are passionate about doing things that matter and solving problems that make a difference for lives, cities and business. We are designers, doctors, data scientists, engineers, developers, thinkers, doers and a whole lot more. If you are curious about the small details of big problems, keen to embrace unknown unknowns as a part of your job and really care about what you do, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what we can solve next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are a first-rate Front End Development Lead ready to join a fast-paced, growing innovation centre. You will operate across all stages of the innovation spectrum, with a remit to build the future in real-time. You will thrive in an open and interactive working environment, which facilitates collaboration with colleagues, clients and ecosystem partners. Our experimentation culture, combined with a disruptive brief, will ensure that together we will make it count.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are a craftsperson, obsessed with bringing the pixel perfect detail of a visual design to life on hybrid mobile and web interfaces. You are experienced in modular, Object Orientated CSS in SASS. Exceptional contemporary JavaScript skills are required. As a front end creative developer, you are also required to work in the Angular or React JavaScript framework and associated libraries such as Flux. Experience with ES2016 / Typescript would therefore be beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are experienced in either the Ionic framework and Cordova, or React Native.&amp;nbsp; You know how to design and implement hybrid applications that will work gracefully on both iOS and Android platforms. WebComponents and Polymer approaches greatly interest you. You will be self-directed, experienced in Agile delivery and capable of a two-way creative coding approach alongside a designer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pair programming and pair design is the philosophy so cross disciplinary understanding is essential.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working with evolving requirements and offering communication on functional suggestions to design is a responsibility of the creative developers we require. You have pride in the quality of your code and are vocal in championing the best approaches, but also appreciate the need to think creatively. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:58:24 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T15:58:24Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128430/front-end-software-engineer-topfloor-systems</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128430/front-end-software-engineer-topfloor-systems</link><a10:author><a10:name>Topfloor Systems</a10:name></a10:author><category>angular</category><category>reactjs</category><category>node.js</category><category>javascript</category><category>web-development</category><title>Front End Software Engineer at Topfloor Systems (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Topfloor Systems is a Dublin based company, specialising in property management software and has a strong presence both in Ireland and the UK. We are the leader in property management software in Ireland. We are currently experiencing exciting growth in the UK and now wish to expand our team to include an additional specialised Front End Software Engineer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Be part of a team that works on our 4 leading products: Blockman, Letman, MyBlockman &amp;amp; MyLetman.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Influence the roadmap and direction our products take.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Build highly available and scalable applications and infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Deploy your own changes into production as part of our continuous deployment, incremental releases.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Very competitive salary.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Supplied workspace with your preferred development environment.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Excellent advancement opportunities working in small sized growing company.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Willing to be Visa Sponsor.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 11:30:49 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T11:30:49Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128460/creative-technology-lead-accenture-centre-for</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128460/creative-technology-lead-accenture-centre-for</link><a10:author><a10:name>Accenture Centre for Innovation</a10:name></a10:author><category>nosql</category><category>hadoop</category><category>apache-spark</category><category>elasticsearch</category><title>Creative Technology Lead at Accenture Centre for Innovation (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At our Centre for Innovation in Dublin, we are passionate about doing things that matter and solving problems that make a difference for lives, cities and business. We are designers, doctors, data scientists, engineers, developers, thinkers, doers and a whole lot more. If you are curious about the small details of big problems, keen to embrace unknown unknowns as a part of your job and really care about what you do, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what we can solve next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are a top-class Creative Technology Lead ready to join a fast-paced, growing innovation centre. You will operate across all stages of the innovation spectrum, with a remit to build the future in real-time. You will thrive in an open and interactive working environment, which facilitates collaboration with colleagues, clients and ecosystem partners. Our experimentation culture, combined with a disruptive brief, will ensure that together we will make it count.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Be Doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creative Technology is a critical function that helps to bring life to our design work, as quickly and tangibly as possible, with an early understanding on feasibility and technical implications. You will drive prototyping as an integral step in the process of conceptualizing, refining and finalizing a designed service or product. You are a craftsperson, capable of a two-way creative coding approach alongside other designer roles. Pair programming and pair design is the philosophy so cross-disciplinary understanding is essential.&amp;nbsp; Working with evolving requirements and offering communication on functional suggestions to design is a responsibility of the creative technologists we require. You have pride in the quality of your code and are vocal in championing the best approaches, but also appreciate the need to think creatively.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:43:22 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T15:43:22Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124437/senior-cloud-security-engineer-workday</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124437/senior-cloud-security-engineer-workday</link><a10:author><a10:name>Workday</a10:name></a10:author><category>oauth</category><category>cryptography</category><category>cloud</category><category>security</category><category>architecture</category><title>Senior Cloud Security Engineer at Workday (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join our team and experience Workday!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's fun to work in a company where people truly believe in what they're doing. At Workday, we're committed to bringing passion and customer focus to the business of enterprise&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We work hard, and we're serious about what we do. But we like to have a good time too. In fact, we run our company with that principle in mind every day: One of our core values is fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Workday Security Engineering team is looking for a seasoned Senior Security Engineer with deep practical experience in application security, specifically in emerging cloud technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This role&amp;rsquo;s charter is to develop, build and deploy security specific solutions and infrastructure, as well as perform security risk analysis, architectural reviews and provide security advisory services to our development teams and cloud architects.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 13:24:49 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-06T13:24:49Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124429/software-developer-x4-work-on-pivotal-cloud-pivotal</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124429/software-developer-x4-work-on-pivotal-cloud-pivotal</link><a10:author><a10:name>Pivotal</a10:name></a10:author><category>go</category><category>ruby</category><category>java</category><category>tdd</category><category>pair-programming</category><title>Software Developer x4 - work on Pivotal Cloud Foundry at Pivotal (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Cloud Foundry engineering team in Pivotal Dublin is looking for several great engineers to join us in building an open source platform that transforms how the world deploys and scales software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for either Software Engineers or Operations / System Engineers who want to learn new skills!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://vimeo.com/69641485" rel="nofollow"&gt;Watch this short video from the engineers at Pivotal!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7APZD0me1nU" rel="nofollow"&gt;Pivotal Cloud Foundry overview by Onsi Fakhouri&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are based in the CHQ Building in Dublin 1 (right beside the red Luas line and Connolly dart station).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You love shipping features, but know that well factored code is what lets you keep shipping features in the long run. &amp;nbsp;Maybe you get antsy writing code without tests, or perhaps you&amp;rsquo;re a large-scale system operator interested in leveling-up your coding skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Either way, you measure &amp;nbsp;your success by the success of your team; you are dedicated to learning about distributed systems, and you are excited to work on open source and be connected to the open source community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cloud Foundry is an open source project co-developed with Pivotal Labs, a leader in the field of agile software development. We are opinionated about how software should be built. We pair program, all day, every day, because we know it delivers remarkable results and supports a cooperative learning environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We work in small teams and rotate between them frequently in order to help you gain a diverse set of skills, and to encourage cross team communication and cohesion. &amp;nbsp;We are committed to working at a sustainable pace &amp;ndash; you&amp;rsquo;ll typically code for 8 hours each day, but then you&amp;rsquo;re off work to relax, recharge, and refocus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the Dublin team, you'll be immersed in all the latest database technologies &amp;mdash; From Cassandra, Redis, RabbitMQ, and more. &amp;nbsp;A proficient understanding of these services, as well as VM and container technologies (Docker), is a plus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desired Skills/ Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are looking for people with either Operations experience or Software Engineers - but you must be interested in the other and be excited to learning new skills. If you have development and operations experience - amazing!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We use Golang, Ruby and Java but you don't have to have experience with these technologies - if you have great experience in other programming languages we can train you up on the technologies we use&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience and/or interest in: Test Driven Development (TDD) and agile methodologies, database technologies, and containerization&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;BA/BS in Computer Science or related field, or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make sure you start your day energized, we provide a catered breakfast every weekday morning, and unlimited snacks/drinks are available all day. Our collaborative, open-plan office space is filled with talented, like-minded engineers who enjoy taking advantage of our weekly lunchtime talks, playing ping pong, and hanging out with their co-workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;We also offer benefits including healthcare, pension and equity in a high growth market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re seeking more amazing developers that complement our Dublin team. Apply by sending us a resume and a cover letter.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 10:54:59 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-06T10:54:59Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122962/software-development-engineer-iii-scala-workday</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122962/software-development-engineer-iii-scala-workday</link><a10:author><a10:name>Workday</a10:name></a10:author><category>scala</category><category>akka</category><category>playframework</category><title>Software Development Engineer III - Scala at Workday (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workday - Scala Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workday is built on an exciting ecosystem of multiple technologies running in the Cloud. We are looking for an outstanding Scala Engineer like you to help us to build our distributed, highly-available elastic GRID platform.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate must have a deep knowledge of software development and cloud infrastructures, microservices architectures and Big Data challenges. We expect you to be an excellent analyst, team builder and problem solver, having fluency in Scala and some other JVM based or functional programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the rest of the agile team members (SW Engineers, QA Automation Engineers).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be a problem solver: be able to understand the big picture, analyse problems and improvements and suggest solid alternatives and answers to our daily challenges.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be a team builder: you would prefer to collaborate with product owners, architects, quality assurance and infrastructure than being a lonely wolf.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Introduce and influence process improvements and act as an agent for change to the organization.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 16:14:53 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-13T16:14:53Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122948/software-development-engineer-iii-workday-studio-workday</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/122948/software-development-engineer-iii-workday-studio-workday</link><a10:author><a10:name>Workday</a10:name></a10:author><category>eclipse</category><category>scala</category><title>Software Development Engineer III - Workday Studio at Workday (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Studio team are looking for an experienced developer who will contribute to the design and development of the next generation of tools within&amp;nbsp;Workday's&amp;nbsp;Integration&amp;nbsp;Platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be joining the team who own Workday Studio, the primary tool Integration developers use to&amp;nbsp;build sophisticated and reliable integrations that places Workday within&amp;nbsp;a customer's enterprise landscape. Workday Studio is a successful product with widespread and ever&amp;nbsp;increasing use.&amp;nbsp;It is a&amp;nbsp;visual&amp;nbsp;integrated development&amp;nbsp;environment&amp;nbsp;built&amp;nbsp;atop&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;Eclipse platform, and our plugins are written in Scala. However, we are constantly looking for ways to further enable our users&amp;nbsp;by extending the tools on offer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a developer&amp;nbsp;who will bring expertise in building web-browser based user interfaces to the team, but who is confident enough to learn and&amp;nbsp;co-own the current product offering, and who will&amp;nbsp;understand the&amp;nbsp;context within Workday's rapidly evolving cloud platform architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The various&amp;nbsp;aspects of the role will include:&amp;nbsp;working&amp;nbsp;with product management and the team to understand the domain and the users, actively drive&amp;nbsp;the design conversation, rapidly build prototypes, and deliver and own quality product.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 13:59:42 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-13T13:59:42Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120317/senior-mobile-developers-at-teamworkcom-teamworkcom</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120317/senior-mobile-developers-at-teamworkcom-teamworkcom</link><a10:author><a10:name>Teamwork.com</a10:name></a10:author><title>Senior Mobile Developers at Teamwork.com at Teamwork.com (Cork, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Here at Teamwork.com we've gone as far as we can with Cross-Platform Technologies for our mobile apps.&amp;nbsp; But it's just not good enough.&amp;nbsp; We want to take advantage of the very best that each platform offers.&amp;nbsp; It's not enough to be able to just get stuff done with our apps - we want them to be so good that people become addicted to using them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;So we're going fully native and we're putting together the best mobile team in the country to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're a die-hard iOS or Android developer, this is your dream job: No legacy code, and the freedom and resources to do the best work of your career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Expect:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Willing to learn. You must have an open mind, be able to pick things up quickly and enjoy working with passionate people.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fundamentally, this position is for a senior developer role, so we want to see that you've made some beautiful apps that you're proud of.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ideally we'd also expect you to be familiar with the list below, but the main thing is your portfolio. Show us with the stuff you've done. Definite bonus points for putting together something using our API (http://developer.teamwork.com) - doesn't matter how small.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we we're not looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ninjas. (Although if you want to do some martial arts in your free time that's fine too.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 11:44:04 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-05T11:44:04Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Cork, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/118379/lead-ui-artist-games-digit-game-studios</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/118379/lead-ui-artist-games-digit-game-studios</link><a10:author><a10:name>DIGIT Game Studios</a10:name></a10:author><category>adobe</category><category>user-interface</category><category>photoshop</category><category>adobe-illustrator</category><category>mmo</category><title>Lead UI Artist (Games) at DIGIT Game Studios (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our goals for this role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your goal is to help DIGIT continue the growth of our hit title &lt;a href="https://www.kingsoftherealm.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Kings of the Realm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will bring our title to the next level, h&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;elping DIGIT to truly push the boundaries of UI design&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; in the game&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;As Lead UI Artist, you will be &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;hands on, as well as leading a small experienced team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; of games UI designers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here's what you will be doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;art direction and own the UI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for the game&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapidly &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;deliver intuitive and rewarding user interfaces&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt;to millions of players for all new game features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design f&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ully responsive user interfaces&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, that work seamlessly across multiple mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Concept, create and validate UI designs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for the game (from user flows through to release)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist in &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rapid iterations and testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; ideas (using wireframes and sketches, in-engine mockups etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;clean and easy to implement UI assets,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; which can seamlessly move straight over to the development team and into games production&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Own the UI pipeline&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt;- create and define style guides and monitor consistency and quality across your team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lead and technically&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt;manage a small skilled team of UI designers - review work daily, act as technical mentor and guide, set goals etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guide the UI vision and art direction&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt;across the team (explorations, colour, composition, iconography etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Innovate and try new things - always push the quality bar on every single topic.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 09:59:39 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-18T09:59:39Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128457/lightweight-architect-accenture-centre-for</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128457/lightweight-architect-accenture-centre-for</link><a10:author><a10:name>Accenture Centre for Innovation</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><category>groovy</category><category>ruby</category><category>php</category><category>python</category><title>Lightweight Architect at Accenture Centre for Innovation (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At our Centre for Innovation in Dublin, we are passionate about doing things that matter and solving problems that make a difference for lives, cities and business. We are designers, doctors, data scientists, engineers, developers, thinkers, doers and a whole lot more. If you are curious about the small details of big problems, keen to embrace unknown unknowns as a part of your job and really care about what you do, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what we can solve next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a Lightweight Architect to join our growing organisation. &amp;nbsp;Operating across all stages of the innovation spectrum, with a remit to build the future in real-time. The working environment will be open and interactive facilitating collaboration with colleagues, clients and ecosystem partners. Our experimentation culture, combined with a disruptive brief will ensure that together we make major societal impacts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be a highly collaborative, open and talented, creative and energetic technology architect with a strong interest in new and emerging technologies. You have broad skills and experience with many software and infrastructure products, technologies and services and you are capable of shaping and delivering innovative technology solutions of heterogeneous components in an Agile, full of challenges environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities will include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Act as the architecture quality keeper for solutions designed and built by different teams;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review the detailed architecture for how components work with each other in given solutions;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review the Technical Design of complex components and features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Architecting reusable components and services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help project teams in ensuring performance, scalability and maintainability of code produced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help the centre&amp;rsquo;s adherence to relevant Good Design Patterns and Principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to switch between different project teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:40:09 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T15:40:09Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/116080/teamwork-projects-software-developer-teamworkcom</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/116080/teamwork-projects-software-developer-teamworkcom</link><a10:author><a10:name>Teamwork.com</a10:name></a10:author><category>knockout.js</category><category>go</category><category>javascript</category><category>mysql</category><category>coffeescript</category><title>Teamwork Projects Software Developer at Teamwork.com (Cork, Ireland) (allows remote)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Technical Stack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don't be deterred if you are not familiar with everything in our tech stack or if you feel as though you are stronger in one area than another. We believe that a passionate and talented developer can learn new practices and technologies. Similarly, we don't place a lot of importance on educational background - as a developer your experience, portfolio, and abilities are key, not your grades :). We do need to see some experience of working in web development and creating or contributing to web applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;HTML&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;CSS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;LESS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;CoffeeScript&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knockout.js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gulp&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Git&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Require.js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;ColdFusion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;MySQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Redis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vagrant/Docker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our entire team works daily with HTML, CSS/LESS, JavaScript (particularly Knockout.js),RESTful APIs, and integrations, and so, experience in full stack web development is important. However, if you are particularly skilled in front-end developent or you are a highly experienced back-end developer, we'd love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teamwork Projects is our flagship product and is used by many of the world's biggest companies, with over 370,000 installations, two million daily users and more than three million unique projects. Despite the vast array of features available in Teamwork Projects, it has been built entirely by a small team of talented developers. We pride ourselves on giving our users what they need and are constantly working on new features and improvements for our customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;By joining our team, you can be assured not only that your work will be seen and enjoyed by millions of users worldwide, but that you will learn and grow continuously, in a friendly, open environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We care about all our teams, and they care about when their teammates will be online, what their timezone is and where they will be working from. When you apply we will ask you about where you intend to work from. We will also ask you whether or not you are open to considering spending some time in our Irish office, if you would like to work remotely, if you would like to relocate or if you're already here and ready to start work at Teamwork HQ in Cork, Ireland.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:27:59 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-09T14:27:59Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Cork, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128465/infrastructure-cloud-support-engineer-accenture-centre-for</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128465/infrastructure-cloud-support-engineer-accenture-centre-for</link><a10:author><a10:name>Accenture Centre for Innovation</a10:name></a10:author><category>amazon-web-services</category><category>azure</category><category>chef</category><category>puppet</category><category>openshift</category><title>Infrastructure/ Cloud Support Engineer at Accenture Centre for Innovation (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At our Centre for Innovation in Dublin, we are passionate about doing things that matter and solving problems that make a difference for lives, cities and business. We are designers, doctors, data scientists, engineers, developers, thinkers, doers and a whole lot more. If you are curious about the small details of big problems, keen to embrace unknown unknowns as a part of your job and really care about what you do, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what we can solve next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an Infrastructure/Cloud Support Engineer to join our growing organisation.&amp;nbsp; Operating across all stages of the innovation spectrum, with a remit to build the future in real-time. The working environment will be open and interactive facilitating collaboration with colleagues, clients and ecosystem partners. Our experimentation culture, combined with a disruptive brief will ensure that together we make major societal impacts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Highly collaborative, open and talent led agile developers, who are ready to lead the way in advancing the next generation of agile practices. We are passionate about Iterative Development and Continuous Improvement. We can and will do whatever it takes to deliver truly great solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&amp;rsquo;ll be doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deliver and ensure quality service using a variety of cloud hosted solutions and software products. Collaborate on design and implementation of multi-tenant environments typically coordinating efforts with different cloud hosting and broker providers, infrastructure outsourcing teams and product support group.&amp;nbsp;Provide ongoing technical support and maintenance of production and development systems and software products (both remote and onsite) and for configured services running on various platforms (operating within a defined operating model and processes). Provide hardware/software support and implement technology at the operating system-level across all server and network areas, and for particular software solutions/vendors/brands. Work includes L1 and L2/ basic and intermediate level troubleshooting.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 16:04:23 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T16:04:23Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128461/dev-ops-support-manager-accenture-centre-for</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/128461/dev-ops-support-manager-accenture-centre-for</link><a10:author><a10:name>Accenture Centre for Innovation</a10:name></a10:author><category>kanban</category><category>docker</category><category>puppet</category><category>chef</category><category>jenkins</category><category>sysadmin</category><title>Dev Ops Support Manager at Accenture Centre for Innovation (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At our Centre for Innovation in Dublin, we are passionate about doing things that matter and solving problems that make a difference for lives, cities and business. We are designers, doctors, data scientists, engineers, developers, thinkers, doers and a whole lot more. If you are curious about the small details of big problems, keen to embrace unknown unknowns as a part of your job and really care about what you do, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what we can solve next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to join top innovators making a global impact?&amp;nbsp; We are looking for highly collaborative, open and talent-led agile developers, who are ready to lead the way in advancing the next generation of agile practices. We are passionate about Iterative Development and Continuous Improvement. We can and will do whatever it takes to deliver truly great solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be architecting, designing and owning a cutting edge Development Operations and Support framework to be used across all projects run by the Centre. You&amp;rsquo;ll also develop, deploy and support infrastructures, applications, software solutions and technology initiatives from an architectural and operational perspective in conjunction with existing standards and methods of delivery; support technical escalation of L3/advanced issues for problem resolution and apply deep knowledge of industry standards and vendor certifications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:45:56 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T15:45:56Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112313/teamwork-desk-software-engineer-teamworkcom</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/112313/teamwork-desk-software-engineer-teamworkcom</link><a10:author><a10:name>Teamwork.com</a10:name></a10:author><category>go</category><category>coffeescript</category><category>knockout.js</category><category>mysql</category><category>rabbitmq</category><title>Teamwork Desk Software Engineer at Teamwork.com (Cork, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Job&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come help us build the best HelpDesk software in the world. The product we built handles millions of support emails a month for thousands of companies. Join a small team of talented developers, doing what we love every day. You will be writing code most of your day :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;What started out initially as a single web app has evolved into an architecture with many small services working with message queues, in-depth metrics, monitoring and logging. We need you to help us build some of the incredible new features we have planned and continue developing this architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Tech Stack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go (we &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; Go)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;CoffeeScript&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;KnockoutJS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;RabbitMQ&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;MySQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Redis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;ElasticSearch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;AWS EC2, ECS, S3, RDS, CodeDeploy, AutoScale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Docker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet some of the Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.teamwork.com/blog/meet-team-brandon-hansen/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Brandon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.teamwork.com/blog/meet-the-team-yannick/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Yannick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.teamwork.com/blog/meet-the-team-peter-kelly/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Peter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some things published by the Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Teamwork Engineering Blog&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://engineroom.teamwork.com/building-desk-from-dream-to-details/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Building Desk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://engineroom.teamwork.com/spam-you-shall-not-pass/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Spam: You Shall Not Pass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://engineroom.teamwork.com/the-go-experiment/" rel="nofollow"&gt;The Go Experiment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a title="Go Learn" href="http://engineroom.teamwork.com/go-learn/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Go Learn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Github (insert open-source stuff we&amp;rsquo;ve released in desk)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/Teamwork/stripehooks" rel="nofollow"&gt;stripehelper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/Teamwork/s3pp" rel="nofollow"&gt;s3pp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/Teamwork/tnef" rel="nofollow"&gt;tnef&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We care about all our teams, and they care about when their teammates will be online, what their timezone is and where they will be working from. When you apply we will ask you about where you intend to work from. We will also ask you whether or not you are open to considering spending some time in our Irish office, if you would like to work remotely, if you would like to relocate or if you're already here and ready to start work at Teamwork HQ in Cork, Ireland.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 16:20:14 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-13T16:20:14Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Cork, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126564/systems-engineer-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126564/systems-engineer-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>linux</category><category>mysql</category><title>Systems Engineer at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>AWS Security is looking for a passionate and driven individual to join its systems engineering team to oversee the daily operations of our physical access control system (PACS) as well as help us design and develop a sustainable and robust architecture for future deployments. As a systems engineer, you will be responsible for the overall health and operations of our PACS. You will be creating availability and health metrics, monitoring performance, performing regular system maintenance, and architecting innovative solutions for running a PACS in a large distributed environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll be looked to as a leader in system knowledge. You will help others learn to program access control hardware and the most optimal way to configure devices and services. You&amp;rsquo;ll work closely with internal customers to help define requirements and see those requirements through to delivery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This position will require participating in a 24/7 on-call rotation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in a related field or 4+ years&amp;rsquo; experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;4+ years&amp;rsquo; experience with Windows Server (2003, 2008, 2008 R2, 2012)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;2+ years&amp;rsquo; experience with relational databases (SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;US citizenship or green card holder&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;3+ years&amp;rsquo; experience with a Physical Access Control system (Lenel, S2, RedCloud, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;3+ Years scripting experience (PowerShell, Batch, Perl, Python, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;3+ Years&amp;rsquo; experience with *NIX systems administration and or development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Experience in 24/7 online environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Lenel certification (Silver, Gold, Master)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Experience using Amazon Web Services (S3, EC2, VPC, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Demonstrate effective oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Proven ability to troubleshoot and identify the root cause of issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Proven experience creating documentation for production systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Proven experience creating end-user training and documentation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Please email AWS Recruiter, Kelly Milne (milnek@amazon.com if you have questions.*&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on Amazon Web Services please visit: http://aws.amazon.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;aws-networkse-na</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:54:30 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-09T14:54:30Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126563/systems-engineer-amazon-web-services-aws-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126563/systems-engineer-amazon-web-services-aws-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>linux</category><category>python</category><category>scripting</category><title>Systems Engineer  Amazon Web Services (AWS) CloudWatch at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Come change the way the world sees the Cloud!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CloudWatch is the monitoring service that AWS customers use to gain system-wide visibility into resource utilization, application performance, and operational health. A picture is worth a thousand words, so CloudWatch gives customers easy easy-to-use graphs to see how their systems are working. With its automatic alarms, CloudWatch helps customers keep their systems running 24x7.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The CloudWatch team is currently looking for a systems engineer with SYSTEM AVAILABILITY OBSESSION DISORDER. Is that you? How can you tell? You delight in operating some of the largest, distributed systems on the planet such as multi-terabyte storage farms and/or horizontally scaled request processing fleets. You detest outages and high latency like the plague, so it&amp;rsquo;s your life&amp;rsquo;s mission to find and eliminate root causes of problems. For you, automation is a way of life, not a nice-to-have, so you&amp;rsquo;ve acquired amazing scripting skills. You follow evolution of the industry to find useful tools that can enhance efficiency. You find data center build-outs, performance engineering, and other scaling activities to be almost as fun as Mardi Gras. Finally, you insist upon giving customers what they want: high quality, highly usable, always-on services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this position you&amp;rsquo;ll get to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Work with developers to design, build, and manage massively scaled monitoring services&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Automate all aspects of systems management&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Build monitoring systems in new data centers and regions, and add/manage capacity in existing regions as our usage grows&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Optimize the performance of our systems by analyzing and deploying new hardware configurations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Track the health of our services, identify problems, drive to root cause, and fix&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Collaborate with some of the leading minds in distributed systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Tell your grandkids that you were you &amp;ldquo;helped create the Cloud all those years ago&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Minimum of 3 years of scripting experience in a Linux environment (in Python, Ruby, Perl, bash, etc.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Minimum of 3 years building and running systems for Internet-facing services&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; BS in computer science or other technical degree and/or related experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Development of systems management and administration automation in a high level scripting language (Python, Ruby, Perl) or Java&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Experience with Linux, network troubleshooting and administration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Experience with systems management and monitoring software (home-grown or commercially available)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Experience with performance testing and tuning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Automation or monitoring framework experience, deployment or development&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 14:46:07 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-09T14:46:07Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126566/aws-production-engineer-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/126566/aws-production-engineer-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>linux</category><category>networking</category><title>AWS Production Engineer at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Production Engineer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon Web Services&amp;rsquo; Technical Operations team (TechOps) is Amazon&amp;rsquo;s central defense against large-scale incidents as well as driving operational excellence across all of Amazon businesses. Our key offering to Amazon is best-in-class Incident Management. Our engineers are front-and-center in driving down event duration through experience in operational excellence, best current practices and incident management tools. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for engineers who have owned or participated in operational and incident management for at least one large-scale enterprise. You should have a passion for working with new technologies and are not afraid to exercise your creativity in pushing the boundaries of existing technologies. Running incident management for AWS is unique in that AWS supports more than 30% of the internet&amp;rsquo;s businesses, and our ability to identify and mitigate issues is the most important aspect of every Amazon employee. Because of our unique role, you will have limitless exposure to all things Amazon. TechOps engineers are encouraged to build solutions to problems while sharing the benefit of those solutions with other AWS service teams. This is an excellent opportunity to join one of Amazon&amp;rsquo;s world-class team of engineers, and work with some of the best and brightest while also developing your skills and career within one of the most dynamic, innovative and progressive technology companies anywhere. In addition to a stimulating and fun working environment, Amazon offers mentoring programs with experienced engineers, regular tech talks with technology Principals, and well-defined career paths for motivated engineers who want to contribute to our culture of operational excellence and relentless customer-focused technical innovation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Provide critical support, incident response, and management to internal customers across all of Amazon including management of communications and coordination of service owners via conference calls&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Be a technology evangelist and use your deep knowledge to solve business problems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Reduce mean time to resolution for all incident types&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Update and/or build world class listening systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Participate in Agile sprints to evolve business processes and technologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Get there first; be the first to detect and diagnose high-severity service-impacting events&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Identify and troubleshoot recurring platform issues and engage service owners to assist with resolution&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Automate tasks through creation and maintenance of scripts and tools&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Respond to and complete customer requests within SLA via a trouble ticketing system&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Take part in a &amp;ldquo;follow the sun&amp;rdquo; rotation split between Seattle, Dublin and Sydney sites, including weekends and holidays&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Create and review documentation, design new standard operating procedures&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Mentor peers in your areas of technical and operational strength&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Participate in the interviewing process&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Primary Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Required:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; A degree in Computer Science or at least two years relevant experience in a large-scale online technical operations environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Excellent English language written and verbal communication skills to facilitate efficient and effective interaction with peers and customers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Confidence to initiate, drive, and manage company-wide conference calls&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Effective organizational skills to maintain a consistently high standard of operations in a busy environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Knowledge of the Linux operating system and good understanding of networking concepts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Excellent troubleshooting skills and a commitment to document findings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Highly desirable:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Knowledge of best current practice frameworks (ITIL, COBIT), particularly incident, problem and change management&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Development/scripting skills in at least one interpreted language (e.g. Perl/Python/Ruby) as well as shell. Working knowledge of a compiled language is a plus&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Understanding of routing protocols to help facilitate troubleshooting and remediation of networking issues&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience in Agile/Scrum or related collaborative workflow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience driving collaborative projects from conception to delivery&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; The ability to maintain a high level of alertness and attention to detail for extended periods&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience dealing effectively with customers during problem resolution and operating efficiently under pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Effective prioritization and time management&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 15:11:15 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-09T15:11:15Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124567/system-development-engineer-aws-network-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124567/system-development-engineer-aws-network-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>linux</category><category>python</category><category>c++</category><title>System Development Engineer, AWS Network Monitoring at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Amazon is looking for Systems and Software Engineers to build and scale the software that monitors one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest and most complex networks. Tens of millions of customers rely on Amazon&amp;rsquo;s network for using our retail websites, accessing content on their Kindles and building applications and businesses on top of Amazon Web Services (AWS). Our goal is to become The Infrastructure Platform for the world - achieving this goal requires high-leverage, massively scalable software systems. Our success depends on our world-class network infrastructure, and our network depends on our Network Monitoring Scaling team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- You are interested in being part of a high-bar team with global responsibility for the Network Monitoring software used across all of Amazon&amp;rsquo;s businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Solving problems at scale excites you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- You do not implement specs from analysts and architects - you talk to your customers and design solutions to their problems. You automate and innovate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- You do not push just one technology agenda - you choose the best tool for the problem at hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- You believe that the craft of software engineering is about writing code right the first time. For you, code reviews and automated testing are not chores - they are a core part of writing great software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- You do not throw your code over the wall. You launch it, own it, support it and make it incrementally better for the benefit of your customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- You enjoy working in a flexible, fast-paced, collaborative team environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Very strong problem solving and coding skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Bash experience plus knowledge of at least one scripting language (Python, Perl, Ruby)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Experience with at least one programming language (Java, C++)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Strong track record of working in areas of significant complexity and &amp;#39;getting things done&amp;#39;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Record of mentoring other engineers to maintain architectural vision and software quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Understanding of data structures, algorithms and their performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Proficient at designing software systems - from high-availability large-scale distributed systems to bespoke scripted solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Advanced UNIX (preferably Linux) systems engineering skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- A strong understanding of core internet technologies (e.g. TCP/IP).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Understanding of the building blocks of computer systems; comfortable working with bits &amp;amp; bytes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Computer Science degree, or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The desire to work in a fast paced and constantly evolving agile environment&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 20:27:49 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T20:27:49Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124566/sr-system-dev-engineer-unified-communications-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/124566/sr-system-dev-engineer-unified-communications-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>linux</category><category>python</category><category>video</category><title>Sr. System Dev Engineer - Unified Communications at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Do you have a voice engineering background and want a new challenge? Do you enjoy learning about new technologies in a challenging, real-world environment? The Unified Communications team at Amazon is looking for a senior engineer who is passionate about VoIP, takes pride in building reliable systems, and enjoys working with dedicated team members. The position will engineer and support voice infrastructure in a worldwide, fast paced, high growth environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Building multi-vendor voice and video solutions hosted on Amazon Web Services to support Amazon&amp;#39;s worldwide growth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Monitoring the performance of Amazon&amp;#39;s voice and video infrastructure to ensure we deliver the highest quality customer experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Developing high-quality self-service tools that enable Amazonians to easily manage their unified communications experience and features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Working directly with vendors and cross-functional teams to support ongoing design and operational excellence efforts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Providing technical leadership and mentoring junior engineers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BASIC QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;#39;s Degree in a technical field or relevant work experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;5+ years telecommunications or voice network administration experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;5+ years managing large-scale enterprise or carrier hosted VoIP and/or video platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of TCP/IP, UDP, SIP, and RTP&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong Linux systems administration skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Good interpersonal and customer service skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong scripting abilities with Perl, Python or another language&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Expertise in many of the following technologies and protocols: BGP, OSPF, SIP, RTP, IP, TCP (internals and flow control), UDP, DNS, DHCP, T1/E1, Ethernet, firewalls, IT security best practices and videoconferencing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Experience in lab-testing &amp;amp; certification of networking/voice devices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Experience in Linux systems administration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Experience working with carriers to provision, install, and operate both voice and data networks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Experience managing complex technical projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of TDM and telecommunications fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 20:27:33 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-07T20:27:33Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/118463/java-developers-datalex</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/118463/java-developers-datalex</link><a10:author><a10:name>Datalex</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><category>rest</category><category>xml</category><category>webservices</category><category>database</category><title>Java Developers at Datalex (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Datalex is an industry leader,&amp;nbsp;we're shaking up the way&amp;nbsp;you will&amp;nbsp;shop&amp;nbsp;for travel products and we're looking for Software Developers to build on our existing team in Dublin.&amp;nbsp;We have&amp;nbsp;a number of vacancies for experienced, highly motivated Software Developers to work in an exciting and dynamic environment. The successful candidate will enjoy working within a team and solving challenging problems that address consumer and social buying behaviors. They will also have a track record in developing high quality software, working within tight deadlines, and have a continuous improvement and customer-focused mindset.&amp;nbsp; Experience in the travel or retail industry would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Estimate, design, implement and test small to medium sized features to the highest standards.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand the business drivers behind each feature.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure the highest levels of quality in development through test-driven development and continuous integration.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contribute towards initiatives to improve the software development process.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand the impact of performance, stability and availability for mission-critical systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 12:34:12 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-12T12:34:12Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114174/senior-network-development-engineer-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/114174/senior-network-development-engineer-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>html</category><category>networking</category><category>deployment</category><title>Senior Network Development Engineer at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Amazon Web Services is searching for industry-leading Senior Network Engineers and Architects to join our network team. We own the design, scalability, and availability of the global networks that power Amazon Web Services. We push our networks to their limit; traditional network vendors simply cannot deliver cost effective solutions capable of meeting our requirements for capacity, availability, or performance. In AWS Networking, we invent, design, refine and then we invent again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, possesses strong written and verbal communication skills, strong project management and time management skills and has a successful track record of designing and delivering simple, scalable solutions. The desire and ability to work in a fast paced, collaborative environment is essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a fantastic opportunity to work with some of the best engineers in the industry and help shape the direction of one of the largest and fastest growing cloud networks in the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- As a Senior Network Engineer working in AWS Networking you will have end to end ownership (architecture/design/scale) of our current and newly developing networks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Lead the design of highly available ultra-scale networks, driving them from concept to launch&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Define and influence strategy within and outside the team&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Lead project teams to deliver impactful benefits to our customers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Work closely with our software developers to full automate network deployment and operations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Drive operational excellence projects to improve network performance and reliability&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Troubleshoot complex problems and develop innovative solutions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Mentoring and coaching junior engineers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Review and implement changes on the network&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Substantial background in large scale network design&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Informal project management experience or experience leading project teams&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Proven experience designing and delivering complex network projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- In-depth knowledge of and significant experience with major Internet protocols: BGP, OSPF, ISIS, MPLS, TCP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Deep knowledge of network hardware and packet forwarding architectures&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Must be comfortable working in a Linux/Unix environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Demonstrated experience creating software to automate network deployment or operations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Must be willing to support an off-hours, engagement only pager rotation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Experience dealing with customers during problem resolution and operating efficiently under pressure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Highly autonomous, very detail oriented, possesses strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Excellent analytical skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Excellent written and verbal communication skills and an ability to interact efficiently with peers and customers is required, as well as experience initiating, driving and managing in-event conference calls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The desire and ability to work in a fast paced, collaborative environment is essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Effective prioritization and time management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 22:08:04 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-15T22:08:04Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109247/cloud-support-engineer-amazon-web-services-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109247/cloud-support-engineer-amazon-web-services-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>chef</category><category>puppet</category><category>os</category><title>Cloud Support Engineer - Amazon Web Services at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Amazon has built a reputation for excellence with recent examples of being named #1 in customer service, #1 most trusted, and #2 most innovative. Amazon Web Services (AWS) is carrying on that tradition while leading the world in Cloud technologies. As a member of the AWS Support team you will be at the forefront of this transformational technology assisting a global list of companies that are taking advantage of a growing set of services and features to run their mission-critical applications. You will work with leading companies in this space and directly with the engineering teams within Amazon developing these new capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The AWS Support team is seeking engineers that enjoy solving problems, working with customers, and have a strong technical background in application management and software development including Git, SVN, and at least one popular programming language. Do you have experience as a Systems Administrator working with Linux, Unix or Windows, and understand the advantages of working in a highly distributed virtual environment? Can you read and troubleshoot code snippets? If you fit the description, you might be the person we are looking for!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will be surrounded by people who are wickedly smart, passionate about cloud computing, and believe that world class support is critical to customer success. Every day will bring new and exciting challenges on the job while you:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Learn and use groundbreaking technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Interact with engineers from leading technology companies around the world&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Field and manage technical customer issues via phone, chat and email&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Apply advanced troubleshooting techniques to provide unique solutions to our customers&amp;#39; individual needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot application deployments, recreate customer issues, build proof of concept applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Leverage your day-to-day experiences to provide the voice of the customer to internal AWS teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Drive customer communication during critical events&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Write tutorials, how-to videos, and other technical articles for the AWS customer community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Work on critical, highly complex customer problems that will span multiple AWS services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Position based in Dublin, Ireland&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;aws-support-eu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Information Science / Information Technology, Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics, Physics, or a related field or relevant experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in a technical position&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Passionate about customers and new technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one of the following languages: Java, .NET, Node.js, PHP, Python, Ruby&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Familiarity with 1 or more version control (Git, Perforce, SVN, TFVC)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Chef/Puppet experience or DevOps background&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Experience with Docker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Exposure to Virtualization (Hypervisors, VMware, Xen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Experience managing full 3 tier application stacks from the OS up through custom applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Demonstrated proficiency in systems administration (Linux/Windows), network administration (DNS, IPsec, BGP, VPN, Load Balancing)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;aws-support-ea</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 07:56:27 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-14T07:56:27Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120550/senior-software-development-engineer-aws-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/120550/senior-software-development-engineer-aws-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>java</category><category>linux</category><category>python</category><title>Senior Software Development Engineer, AWS Networking at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Amazon is looking for Software Development Engineers to build the software that monitors one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest and most complex networks. Tens of millions of customers rely on Amazon&amp;rsquo;s network for using our retail websites, accessing content on their Kindles and building applications and businesses on top of Amazon Web Services (AWS). Our goal is to become The Infrastructure Platform for the world - achieving this goal requires high-leverage, massively scalable software systems. Our success depends on our world-class network infrastructure, and our network depends on our Network Monitoring team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You are interested in being part of a high-bar team with global responsibility for the Network Monitoring software used across all of Amazon&amp;rsquo;s businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Solving problems at scale excites you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You don&amp;rsquo;t implement specs from analysts and architects - you talk to your customers and design solutions to their problems. You automate and innovate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You do not push just one technology agenda - you choose the best tool for the problem at hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You believe that the craft of software engineering is about writing code right the first time. For you, code reviews and automated testing are not chores - they&amp;rsquo;re a core part of writing great software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You don&amp;rsquo;t throw your code over the wall. You launch it, own it, support it and make it incrementally better for the benefit of your customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You enjoy working in a flexible, fast-paced, collaborative team environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Computer Science degree, or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Ability to gather customer requirements and deliver innovative solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Strong track record of launching projects of significant complexity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Ability to mentor other software developers to maintain architectural vision and software quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Experience with software engineering best practices (code reviews, source control management, build processes, testing, release and change management).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Very strong problem solving and coding skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Understanding of data structures, algorithms and their performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Proficient at designing software systems, from high-availability large-scale distributed systems to your application&amp;rsquo;s object model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Understanding of the building blocks of computer systems; comfortable working with bits &amp;amp; bytes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Knowledge of at least one scripting language.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Comfortable with Linux and a good understanding of networking concepts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Experience of working in a DevOps team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Experience developing robust, highly scalable distributed systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;aws-sdesdm-ea&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 10:04:37 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-09T10:04:37Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109561/manager-software-development-load-balancing-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109561/manager-software-development-load-balancing-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>software</category><category>development</category><category>java</category><title>Manager, Software Development, Load Balancing Control Plane Systems at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>AWS Load Balancing Control Plane platform is one of the largest in the industry, managing service endpoints for Amazon services with billions of requests. We are looking for a Software Development Manager to define and build our next-generation control plane software system. This team owns the API&amp;#39;s and systems used for both directly customer-facing services as well as the control plane for many internal services. This is a balanced team of senior and junior engineers that has proven it can deliver very important features for our customers. This leader will own staffing and managing the team for a key part of the service, setting the team culture, best practices, planning, and delivering on the product roadmap. The successful candidate will be comfortable dealing with ambiguity, be very customer-centric and able to think big.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our mission is to enable all Amazon service owners to completely manage load-balancing for their services. We develop highly available and robust APIs so that all Amazon service owners can build/scale service endpoints and safely mange deployments to existing endpoints in a completely automated fashion. Our APIs and UIs make it easy for customers to deploy services that strictly adhere to Amazon availability and security best practices and make it impossible to perform actions that are unsafe, and difficult to set up services that do not adhere to best practice guidelines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ideal candidate will be passionate about the potential of high-scale load balancing solutions as well as about building great resilient, scalable and high-performance services. This leader has thrived and succeeded in delivering high quality technology products/services in a rapid growth environment where priorities shift quickly. We are looking for a strong leader who prioritizes well, communicates clearly and understands how to drive a high level of focus and excellence with a strong team. They are a seasoned, mature engineering leader who is comfortable building teams and developing staff. This person has a proven track record of building a culture centered on customer focus, efficient execution, high quality, rigorous testing, deep monitoring, and solid deployment practices. AWS in general, and this business in particular, operates at very large scale and on critical workloads, so a passion and discipline around operational excellence is key. A high level of ownership and accountability is a must.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a manager of this team, you will be leading a team of highly motivated software developers that thrives on solving challenging problems with innovative solutions building large-scale distributed software systems in Python, Java and other languages using open source technologies like Apache, Celery, Redis, HTTP/REST services etc., and other Amazon&amp;rsquo;s proprietary technologies. You will own, build, and operate a fundamental Tier-0 service - Amazon&amp;#39;s Load Balancing Control Plane Service. You will also provide exceptional leadership &amp;amp; management for the engineers in your team. As a manager of this team, you will have the opportunity to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be great fun to work with. Our company credo is &amp;ldquo;Work hard. Have fun. Make history&amp;rdquo;. The right candidate will love what they do and instinctively know how to make work fun. Enjoy being a really great people manager. Building, motivating and mentoring a world-class systems &amp;amp; software engineering team is the most important part of this role. You should have a proven track record in recruiting and retaining top talent and excel in day-to-day people and performance management tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy building large scale distributed software systems. Drive the development of software framework that allows AWS and Amazon retail systems to use load balancing solutions seamlessly. Identify areas of improvement in our existing frameworks, tool, and processes and strive to make them better. You will enjoy keeping your technical skills reasonably current and can contribute meaningfully to architecture discussions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have strong project &amp;amp; product management experience. The successful candidate will create product roadmaps for the team. This will include helping innovate and invent new value-add services. You will need excellent technical project management skills to deliver product roadmap items as well as other cross-team projects. Experience with Agile methodologies is an advantage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Know how to run a tight, lean, efficient operation. The right candidate will want to measure everything and be very data driven. He/she will excel at using metrics, monitoring and alarming to measure and improve the operational processes and performance of their team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer - Minority / Female / Disability / Vet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit www.amazon.jobs for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;BS/MS in Computer Science or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;5+ years of industry experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of software development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2&amp;mdash;3 years of software management experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Technically sound in software development activities and life cycles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Passion for great customer experience and API usability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Software development experience in Java, XML, Web services, UNIX tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Experience with large scale distributed systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of networking concepts and features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;A passion for people management and mentoring&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong analytic and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Internet and operating system fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 16:10:01 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-20T16:10:01Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109704/software-development-engineer-networking-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109704/software-development-engineer-networking-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>software</category><category>development</category><category>networking</category><title>Software Development Engineer, Networking Software Systems at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>WHAT? A wave of innovation is bringing sweeping changes to networking technology. Virtualization, unimaginable scale, hardware commoditization, and automation are revolutionizing network software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE? At Amazon we push the boundaries in robustness, fault-tolerance and smart adaptive algorithms that can react intelligently to real-world events. Software engineers on our team contribute to every phase of the development process and deploy scalable software systems worldwide.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHY THERE? Amazon Web Services (AWS) runs one of the biggest networks in the world. We leverage big data technologies and deep network analytics software to drive network automation, performance, and reliability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHY CARE? Make history as a software developer at AWS Networking. We develop software at every level of the stack from front-end user interfaces to low-level embedded software and everything in between. We are a highly motivated, co-operative, and fun loving team of software developers who thrive on solving challenging problems and building large-scale distributed software systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer - Minority / Female / Disability / Vet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit www.amazon.jobs for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;A bachelor&amp;#39;s degree or higher in Computer Science (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in building production software applications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Software development skills, preferably in Java, C/C++, Ruby and/or Perl in Linux environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Familiarity with distributed systems, asynchronous messaging, and network protocols.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;A solid grounding in Computer Science fundamentals, data structures, algorithms, object-oriented design and systems architecture.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Problem solving and troubleshooting skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Knowledge of major protocols, topology design, network hardware and device configuration.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in building production software applications with focus on efficient back-end components is required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;A solid understanding of performance and efficiency issues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Experience with distributed computing and enterprise-wide systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Experience taking a leading role in building complex software systems that have been successfully delivered to customers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Experience mentoring junior software engineers to improve their skills, and make them more effective, product software engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Experience influencing software engineering best practices within your team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Ability to take a project from scoping requirements through actual launch of the project.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;A strong customer orientation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**LI-LJ1</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:27:05 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-21T16:27:05Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109197/big-data-devops-support-engineer-amazon-web-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109197/big-data-devops-support-engineer-amazon-web-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>hadoop</category><category>os</category><category>java</category><title>Big-Data Devops Support Engineer - - Amazon Web Services at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Amazon has built a reputation for excellence with recent examples of being named #1 in customer service, #1 most trusted, and #2 most innovative. Amazon Web Services (AWS) is carrying on that tradition while leading the world in Cloud technologies. As a member of the AWS Support team you will be at the forefront of this transformational technology assisting a global list of companies that are taking advantage of a growing set of services and features to run their mission-critical applications. You will work with leading companies in this space and directly with the engineering teams within Amazon developing these new capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AWS Support provides global technical support to a wide range of external customers as they build mission-critical applications on top of AWS services such as Amazon S3 and Amazon EC2. We have a team of talented Support Engineers located in 8 countries around the world, and are growing rapidly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are seeking Devops Support Engineers with an affinity for big-data tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every day will bring new and exciting challenges on the job while you:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Learn and use groundbreaking technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Apply advanced troubleshooting techniques to provide unique solutions to our customers&amp;#39; individual needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Interact with leading technologists around the world&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Work directly with Amazon Web Service architects to help reproduce and resolve customer issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Leverage your extensive customer support experience to provide feedback to internal AWS teams on how to improve our services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Drive customer communication during critical events&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Drive projects that improve support-related processes and our customers&amp;rsquo; technical support experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Write tutorials, how-to videos, and other technical articles for the customer community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Work on critical, highly complex customer problems that may span multiple AWS services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Information Science / Information Technology, Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics, Physics, or a related field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in a technical position&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Strong Linux system administrator skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of Hadoop architecture and administration and support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Proficient in Map-Reduce, Zookeeper, HBASE, HDFS, Pig, Hive,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Python, and shell scripting; experience with Chef a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Expert understanding of ETL principles and how to apply them within Hadoop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Be able to read java code, and basic coding/scripting ability in Java, Perl, Ruby, C#, and/or PHP&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Experienced with linux system monitoring and analysis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Good understanding of distributed computing environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Technology-related Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Customer service experience / strong customer focus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Strong multi-tasking skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Strong analysis and troubleshooting skills and experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Self-starter who is excited about learning new technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Networking (DNS, TCP/IP)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Databases (MySQL, Oracle, MSSQL)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Exposure to Virtualization (VMware, Xen, Hypervisor)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Prior working experience with AWS - any or all of EC2, S3, EBS, ELB, RDS, Dynamo DB, EMR&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Exposure to security concepts / best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Expertise with IPsec, VPN, Load Balancing, Iperf, MTR, Routing Protocols, SSH, Network Monitoring / Troubleshooting tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Experience managing full application stacks from the OS up through custom applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Open to working non-standard hours (no night shifts) including a Sun-Mon or Fri-Sat weekend.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon Web Services is hiring. For more information: http://aws.amazon.com/careers/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*LI-AC2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;aws-support-na</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 15:07:33 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-13T15:07:33Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110034/senior-network-development-engineer-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/110034/senior-network-development-engineer-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>ospf</category><category>bgp</category><category>tcp</category><category>java</category><category>c</category><title>Senior Network Development Engineer at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Amazon.com is looking to hire highly motivated, best-in-class Senior Network Engineers for our Internet Services/Backbone network team to drive the stability and sustainability of our next-generation networks and to discover innovative ways to automate and scale our network as we expand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ideal candidate will be expected to provide high quality first-tier network and network event management for Amazon&amp;rsquo;s worldwide network operations. He/she will demonstrate an excellent knowledge of networking and networking concepts and theory, and have experience participating in operational network support for a large-scale enterprise environment. He/she will have a proven track record of success in driving complex issues to resolution autonomously and/or collaboratively. A love for working with new technologies and pushing the envelope on existing technology is required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an excellent opportunity to join Amazon&amp;rsquo;s world class technical teams, working with some of the best and brightest engineers while also developing your skills and furthering your career within one of the most innovative and progressive technology companies anywhere.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a Senior Network Engineer working in AWS Networking you will:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;have end to end ownership (architecture/design/scale) of our current and newly developing networks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;lead the design of highly available ultra-scale networks, driving them from concept to launch.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;define and influence strategy within and outside the team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;lead project teams to deliver impactful benefits to our customers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;work closely with our software developers to fully automate network deployment and operations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;drive operational excellence projects to improve network performance and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;troubleshoot complex problems and develop innovative solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;mentor and coach junior engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;review and implement changes on the network.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Substantial background in large scale network design.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Informal project management experience or experience leading project teams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Proven experience designing and delivering complex network projects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of and significant experience with major Internet protocols: BGP, OSPF, ISIS, MPLS, TCP.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Deep knowledge of network hardware and packet forwarding architectures.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Must be comfortable working in a Linux/Unix environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience creating software to automate network deployment or operations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Software development/programming/scripting skills are highly desired specifically Perl, or shell (bash, ksh, csh.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;li&gt;Knowledge or awareness of IT best practice frameworks (ITIL, COBIT) and Operational Excellence concepts or methodologies is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Must be willing to support an off-hours, engagement only pager rotation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Experience dealing with customers during problem resolution and operating efficiently under pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other Requirements&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;The ability to sit in front of computer for entire scheduled 12-hour shift with appropriate breaks while maintaining a high level of alertness and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Ability to move and lift computer equipment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Must be able to work in a follow the sun shift (6am-6pm) across and including weekends and holidays.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Must be willing to support an off-hours, engagement only pager rotation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Experience dealing with customers during problem resolution and operating efficiently under pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Effective prioritization and time management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:58:55 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-10-26T16:58:55Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109071/senior-software-development-engineer-aws-amazon</guid><link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/109071/senior-software-development-engineer-aws-amazon</link><a10:author><a10:name>Amazon</a10:name></a10:author><category>python</category><category>java</category><category>linux</category><title>Senior Software Development Engineer, AWS Networking at Amazon (Dublin, Ireland)</title><description>Amazon is looking for Software Development Engineers to build the software that monitors one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest and most complex networks. Tens of millions of customers rely on Amazon&amp;rsquo;s network for using our retail websites, accessing content on their Kindles and building applications and businesses on top of Amazon Web Services (AWS). Our goal is to become The Infrastructure Platform for the world - achieving this goal requires high-leverage, massively scalable software systems. Our success depends on our world-class network infrastructure, and our network depends on our Network Monitoring team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You are interested in being part of a high-bar team with global responsibility for the Network Monitoring software used across all of Amazon&amp;rsquo;s businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Solving problems at scale excites you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You don&amp;rsquo;t implement specs from analysts and architects - you talk to your customers and design solutions to their problems. You automate and innovate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You do not push just one technology agenda - you choose the best tool for the problem at hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You believe that the craft of software engineering is about writing code right the first time. For you, code reviews and automated testing are not chores - they&amp;rsquo;re a core part of writing great software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You don&amp;rsquo;t throw your code over the wall. You launch it, own it, support it and make it incrementally better for the benefit of your customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; You enjoy working in a flexible, fast-paced, collaborative team environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Computer Science degree, or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Ability to gather customer requirements and deliver innovative solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Strong track record of launching projects of significant complexity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Ability to mentor other software developers to maintain architectural vision and software quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Experience with software engineering best practices (code reviews, source control management, build processes, testing, release and change management).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Very strong problem solving and coding skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Understanding of data structures, algorithms and their performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Proficient at designing software systems, from high-availability large-scale distributed systems to your application&amp;rsquo;s object model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Understanding of the building blocks of computer systems; comfortable working with bits &amp;amp; bytes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Knowledge of at least one scripting language.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Comfortable with Linux and a good understanding of networking concepts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Experience of working in a DevOps team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Experience developing robust, highly scalable distributed systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;aws-sdesdm-ea&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 12:59:21 Z</pubDate><a10:updated>2016-11-12T12:59:21Z</a10:updated><location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Dublin, Ireland</location></item></channel></rss>